<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home Page on My New Hugo Site?</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home Page on My New Hugo Site?</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Brain Tumor MRI Images Classification and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/tumor-mri-images-classification-and-segmentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/tumor-mri-images-classification-and-segmentation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;github link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/G-dab/Brain-Tumor-MRI-Images-Classification-and-Segmentation&#34;&gt;https://github.com/G-dab/Brain-Tumor-MRI-Images-Classification-and-Segmentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CV Report:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;ABSTRACT&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Non-invasive imaging techniques, particularly Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI), play a pivotal role in diagnosing brain tumors by providing detailed anatomical and functional insights. In the classification task, we employed the VGG16 neural network architecture and achieved an accuracy of 96% on the test set. For the segmentation task, we referred to the U-Net architecture, designed our own loss function, and incorporated extensive data augmentation techniques. Ultimately, we developed a U-Net3D network architecture that directly processes 3D files. The Dice coefficient reached 83.0% on the training set and 83.2% on the test set.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imitation Learning for Bilateral Coordination</title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/imitation-learning-for-bilateral-coordination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/imitation-learning-for-bilateral-coordination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;design&#34;&gt;Design&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;system-architecture&#34;&gt;System Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid Arm</title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/humanoid-arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/humanoid-arm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project was my internship project during 2024 summer at JAKA Robotics. I designed a small 7DOF humanoid robot arm. What sets it apart from most humanoid arms on the market is the configuration of the degrees of freedom at the wrist. The joints use small green harmonic drive reducers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mechanical-design&#34;&gt;Mechanical Design&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The humanoid arm can be divided into three parts: the shoulder, the upper arm, and the lower arm. The shoulder has 2 degrees of freedom, the upper arm has 2 degrees of freedom, and the lower arm has 3 degrees of freedom.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bionic Frog</title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/bionic_frog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/bionic_frog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We designed a remotely controlled bionic frog jumping robot. The energy storage mechanism utilizes a cam-driven linkage to compress the spring, and remote control is achieved through Wi-Fi or Bluetooth connections. Within the specified dimensions of the project, it has achieved a jumping distance of greater than 52cm.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;requirements&#34;&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project is targeted at the 11th (2024) National College Students&amp;rsquo; Mechanical Innovation Design Competition. The bionic frog&amp;rsquo;s appearance has the following size restrictions:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development of a Digital Twin-based In-situ Wear Testing System</title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/development_of_a_digital-twin-based_in-situ_wear_testing_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/development_of_a_digital-twin-based_in-situ_wear_testing_system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Measurement methods are typically one of the important factors affecting the results of &lt;strong&gt;wear tests&lt;/strong&gt;, divided into in-situ and ex-situ measurements. In-situ measurements do not require changing the contact conditions of the test samples, which can reduce the risk of experimental data being affected, and thus are gradually being applied in more and more research.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital twin technology&lt;/strong&gt; achieves the integration of virtual and physical entities through consistency and synchronization.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
